earthhour.org 2014-05-05

# Privacy Policy | EARTH HOUR

**WWF ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY** | TERMS AND CONDITIONS

**1) This website is owned by Earth Hour Global Limited based in Singapore**

(ACCRA number 201220322W) and WWF-WORLD WIDE FUND FOR NATURE (formerly World Wildlife Fund) of Av. du Mont-Blanc, 1196 Gland, Switzerland (“WWF”), (collectively, "Earth Hour").

**2) We may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this posting.**

Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes.

2a) Earth Hour only collects email addresses from the users of the website and only those addresses which are knowingly and specifically supplied to us by the user.

2b) Earth Hour is committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal information.

2c) We will not sell or pass on your information to any other organization outside of Earth Hour unless you specifically and expressly give us permission to do so.

2d) Once a user enters an email address, they will receive an auto response which will contain general update and news about the Earth Hour campaign

2e) We always give you the option to unsubscribe from our mailing lists.

2f) If you are under 18 years old, you should obtain consent from your parents or guardians. Parents and guardians can choose to sign up at the website.

**3\. What information do we collect?**

3a) Personal information such as first name, last name, e-mail address and mobile phone number. We collect this information only in connection with specific activities, such as membership, campaigns, feedback, surveys, email newsletter subscriptions, etc.

3b) Non-personal information WWF collects data such as IP address (the location of the computer on the internet), pages accessed and files downloaded. This helps us to determine how many individuals use our site, how many people visit on a regular basis, which pages are most popular, and which pages are least popular. This information doesn't tell us anything about who you are, it simply allows us to monitor and improve our service.

3c) Videos, images and text uploaded to [www.earthhour.org](http://www.earthhour.org/) and[ www.youtube.com/earthhour](http://www.youtube.com/earthhour) are collected through various websites, widgets, SMS, APIs, services and third parties. When uploading content to this platform you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information in any country. Your email address and mobile number will not be made public and will only be used by WWF if you opt in to receive communications.

**4\. Where will the information be held?**

Personal information such as email address and mobile number submitted through the sign up forms on this site is held only in a Earth Hour database. We promise that Earth Hour will not share the information you give to us on this website with any other organization outside of WWF unless you have specifically given us permission to do so.

**5\. Information from under 18s**

If you are under 18, be sure to obtain your parents’ or guardians’ permission before you send any information about yourself (your name, address, e-mail address, etc.) to us or anyone else over the internet. We encourage parents to get involved with their children's use of the Internet and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating.

**6\. Your right to access the information**

At any time, you can ask us for a copy of the personal information that we hold about you or request a correction or deletion of information.

**7\. External links**

There are links on this web site that take you to other web sites outside of our service. Any links provided to third party web sites outside of this site are provided solely for your convenience. The operation and content of such third party web sites is beyond our control, and we do not endorse in any manner whatsoever or accept any responsibility for the content or other material that may be contained on such web sites, the use of such web sites, or any products or services advertised on or sold through any such web sites. We will not be liable under any circumstances for any damages whatsoever, direct or indirect, resulting from any use of this web site or any other third party web site linked to this web site, whether or not we are advised of the possibility of such damages.

**8\. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please  [contact us](mailto:contact@earthhour.org?subject=Enquiry%3A%20Privacy%20Policy).**
